# JOHN JONATHAN L. LAZARO

### LICENSED PROFESSIONAL TEACHER









## **PROFILE**

A licensed professional teacher that specializes in educational measurement and evaluation. Skilled in the assessment practices, education, and training industry. With experience in leading, training, mentoring, and researching as a former subject area coordinator, and a people development officer.

# **SKILLS**

- Data-driven decision making skills
- Expertise in assessment methods
- Proficient in test development processes
- Knowledgeable in different statistical methods related to assessment
- Competent is using SPSS, MS
  Office suite, Google
  workspace, and Canva

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### PEOPLE DEVELOPMENT OFFICER

ITFG Global Visa Consultancy

August 2021 - Present

- Assist with the employee onboarding process and conducts training with new hires
- Coordinates with partners and participants on the details that require training
- Monitors the schedule of different trainings provided and ensure post-training evaluation

## **SUBJECT AREA COORDINATOR**

Benedictine Institute of Learning June 2017 - May 2021

- Managed and mentored a team of educators to ensure professional growth and compliance with the standard operating procedures
- Coordinated and planned several activities to achieve results according to the schedule
- Completed tasks to ensure compliance with relevant regulations
- Participated in continuous improvement by engaging in problemsolving skills to support teamwork

# **EDUCATION**

MASTER OF ARTS IN EDUCATION (EDUCATIONAL MEASUREMENT & EVALUATION) - (42 UNITS)

2015 - present Philippine Normal University

# BACHELOR OF SECONDARY EDUCATION (VALUES EDUCATION)

2007 - 2011

Philippine Normal University

## **FACULTY MEMBER**

Benedictine Institute of Learning June 2011 - May 2021

- Incorporated proven methods of engagement and assessment to facilitate student learning
- Selected and developed instructional materials to support student learning
- Created tasks to encourage higher-order thinking skills